<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">HaBEAT</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string name="back_btn_lbl">Back to Main</string>

    <string name="title_activity_deep_breathing">HaBEAT - Deep Breathing Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_self_massage">HaBEAT - Self Massage Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_urge_surfing">Urge Surfing Activity</string>

    <string name="drawerItem1">Support Group</string>
    <string name="drawerItem2">Statistics</string>
    <string name="drawerItem3">Leaderboards</string>
    <string name="drawerItem4">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawerItem5">Home</string>

    <string name="massage_desc_1">
        The heels of your hands do a lot of hard work and
        don\'t get nearly as much attention as your fingers do. Rub them in gentle
        circular motions, beginning on the side furthest from your thumb and working
        your way across.
    </string>
    <string name="massage_desc_2">
        The web of muscle connecting your thumb to the rest of your hand does a lot of
        stretching across the keyboard. Grasp it between your thumb and forefinger and
        move it gently up and down to facilitate release and muscle relaxation.
    </string>
    <string name="massage_desc_3">
        Massaging the muscles and joints at the bases of your fingers can really soothe
        soreness and help relieve cramps. Use a circular stroke, similar to the one you
        did for the heels of your hands.
    </string>
    <string name="massage_desc_4">
        The outer sides of your hands need attention, too. Use an upward circular stroke
        to go from the base of your hand up to the finger joints.
    </string>
    <string name="massage_desc_5">
        Gently pulling on your fingers (never pull hard) stretches the muscles and gives
        joints some much-needed relief.
    </string>
    <string name="massage_desc_6">
        Knit your fingers together and pull gently to stretch and release the muscles in
        your hands. For the most relaxation, focus on making the muscles in your palms stretch
        instead of those in your fingers.
    </string>
    <string name="massage_desc_7">
        Don\'t forget your wrists. Position your hand as if you were about to take your own pulse,
        but instead move all your digits in a soft circular motion, moving from one side of your
        wrist to the other. Repeat all of the above strokes if desired.
    </string>

</resources>
